-=THE LAST FANTASY=-
仅供交流 严禁商用
字幕来源：射手网（随缘翻译，熊猫七兵卫校验）
字幕调校：EvineDeng
这是一个奇迹
It's a wonder...
奇迹，女人
...Wonder Woman...
你太疯狂了，太棒了
You're so wild and wonderful
我看起来什么时候都是这样的
'Cause it seems whenever...
我们在一起
...we're together...
所有的星球都很平静
...the planets all stand still.
芭芭丽娜的迷惑
Barbarella's psychedelia...
这里是一种关于你的柯克贝壳
...there's a kind of cockle shell
about you.
芭芭丽娜
Barbarella... Bar... Barbarella.
你的这些彩虹的色彩让我眩晕了
You dazzle me with rainbow
colors...
让阴暗无光的生活消失吧
Fade away the duller shade
of living...
让我高兴起来
Get me up high...
教我飞
Teach me to fly...
通上电
Electrify...
一个有星空灯的夜晚
A night with starry light...
在平流层之上
...above the stratosphere.
亲近一些
Bring your dearness near
直到黎明来临
Till the dawn comes tumbling down
别出声
Don't make a sound.
深邃的夜空会说出每一句我们想要说的话
Every word we need
comes from the sky.
你不能读懂我的心吗？
Can't you read my mind
你的心告诉我你恋爱了
Say in love
难度你就不能给我一个酷酷的拥抱？
Don't you give me a cold shoulder
丫头，拥抱你我会死的
Still I'm dying, girl, to hold you
And make love...
...Iove...
芭芭丽娜迷惑了
Barbarella's psychedelia...
决对没有哪个家伙叫你这样的名字或者克隆你
...never can a fella name or clone you...
Barbarella Bar... Barbarella
待机等待一个来自于石竹的信息
Stand by for a message from Dianthus...
地球的主席和太阳系的旋转总理
...President of Earth and Rotating Premier of the Sun System.
- 芭芭丽娜？
- 主席先生
- Barbarella?
- Mr. President.
- 爱！
- Love!
请稍等 我要戴上先
Just a minute. I'll slip something on.
别为难你自己 这是整个国家的事
Don't trouble yourself. This is an affair of state.
我必须要说的不但重要 是一个秘密
What I must say not only is grave... It's a secret.
秘密？
A secret?
你曾经听说过一个叫杜兰杜兰的年轻科学家吗？
Have you ever heard of a young scientist named Duran Duran?
- 恩，听说过
- 最近在去往北极星的途中
- Yes.
- Recently en route to the North Star...
他消失了 在Tau Ceti的未知区域
...he vanished into the uncharted regions of Tau Ceti.
但是为什么是个秘密呢？
But... why is that a secret?
因为杜兰杜兰是射线的发明家
Because Duran Duran is the inventor of the Positronic Ray.
- 是一种武器
- 武器？
- It's a weapon.
- Weapon?
为什么有些人要发明武器？
Why would anyone want to invent a weapon?
我怎么知道？
How should I know?
宇宙已经平静了几个世纪，先生
The universe has been pacified for centuries, sir.
据我们所知。我们对于Tau Ceti和它的居民一无所知
As far as we know. Yet we know nothing of Tau Ceti or its inhabitants.
他们可能仍然处于一个原始的精神不受支配的国度？
Could they still be in a primitive state of neurotic irresponsibility?
这正是我要说的，如果他们从这个年轻的科学家身上学习到
Precisely. And If they learn from this young scientist...
射线的秘密
...the secret of the Positronic Ray...
他们就有能力破坏宇宙这个充满爱的大家庭
...they will be able to shatter the loving union of the universe.
- 这可能意味着陈旧的不安全感...
- 战争
- That might mean archaic insecurity...
- And war.
- 你的意思是自私的竞争和。。
- 我是说战争
- You mean selfish competition and...
- I mean war.
- 所有部落之间充满血腥冲突
- 我不相信
- Bloody conflict among entire tribes.
- I don't believe it.
我也不相信  但是我们不能冒险
Neither do I. But we can't take a chance.
- 我们必须做些什么
- 对，你就是必须阻止这些事情发生的女孩
- Something must be done.
- Yes. You're the girl who must do it.
- 为什么是我？
- 我没有武器我也不是警察
- Why me?
- I have no armies or police.
我不能吝啬总统的伙伴. 另外, 你是一个 5星的 飞行员.
I can't spare the presidential band. Plus, you're a 5-star Astro-Navigatrix.
你的任务是：找到杜兰杜兰
Your mission then: Find Duran Duran...
利用你无可比拟的才能来保卫这个宇宙所有星球的安全
...and use your incomparable talents to preserve the security of the stars...
和你自己的星球 你觉得我怎么样？
...and our own mother planet. How do you read me?
- 正直
- 这是一张杜兰杜兰的照片
- Straight.
- Here's the one known photo of Duran.
26岁，眼神深邃 一个相当帅的家伙
Age 26. Hazel eyes. A rather handsome fellow.
我觉得我认不出他来，先生
I don't think I'll be able to recognize him, sir.
这个是便携式脑波探测器
Now, this is a portable brainwave detector.
注意 把你的原子信息传导器设置到0-3-5
Attention... Set your atom transmitter at 0-3-5.
- 一切正常
- 反传导
- Positive.
- Object in transit.
对象收到.
Object received.
只有简单的按下这个接触键就能检测到杜兰是否在场。
In order to test for Duran Duran's presence, simply press this contact.
-指示灯一旦亮了警报就会响起。 -它内部有一个音频测试器
- Light will glow. The alarm will sound.
- It has a built-in tongue box.
这些东西你可能会用到。
Here is something you may need.
- 是武器吗？
- 用来自我保护的
- It's a weapon?
- For self-preservation.
我们从战争博物馆借来的。
We borrowed it from the Museum of Conflict.
我的好姑娘 芭芭丽娜，有一天
That's my good girl. One day, Barbarella...
...我们必须满足肉体
...we must meet in the flesh.
谢谢
Thank you. And... love!
爱!
Love!
被武装起来，像一个赤裸裸的野蛮人
Armed... Like a naked savage.
阿尔法7呼叫基地
Alpha 7 to Base... Alpha 7 to Base.
我们在7分钟之内离开太阳引力区域，确认
We leave the Zone of Solar Attraction in 7 minutes. Acknowledge.
基地呼叫阿尔法7，确认
Base to Alpha 7. Acknowledge.
准备为进入现在的空间加速
Prepare for acceleration into temporal space.
加速进入现在空间
Acceleration into temporal space... Continuum now beginning.
我们什么时候能到达Tau Ceti的引力区域？
Alphy, when do we get to the Tau Ceti gravitational field?
地球时间154小时7分钟之后
154 hours, seven minutes, elapses Earth Time.
.好的
Right.
- 154小时之后叫醒我
- 回答完毕
- Wake me up in 154 hours.
- Confirmed.
- 晚安
- 回答完毕
- Good night, Alphy.
- Confirmed.
直线加速
De-acceleration looks in line...
芭芭丽娜起身，光芒四射。
Barbarella rise and shine.
准备吸入营养物质
Prepare to insert nourishment.
加速结束进入7秒倒计时
End of course in temporal acceleration in 7 seconds.
到Tau Ceti了
Alphy... It's Tau Ceti.
- 怎么了？
- 有电磁干扰
- What's happening?
- Magnetic disturbances.
电磁干扰？
Magnetic disturbances?
应急系统！
Emergency systems!
所以应急系统都准备就绪。
All emergency systems will now operate.
- 我们的电磁屏幕死机了。
- 强制启动磁飓风的密码是119
- Our magnetic screens are dead!
- Force of magnetic hurricane is 1 1.9.
掌舵罗盘失灵
Gyro compass is not, repeat, not functioning.
- 你的意思是导航系统失灵？
- 是的
- You mean you can't navigate?
- That is correct.
我将它转换为手动。 我们成功的机率大吗？
I'll switch it to manual. What are our chances?
我们目前不可破坏的可能性是
Our present possibilities of non-destruction...
...0.00002 到10,000
...are 0.00002 to 10,000.
我的2号稳压器已经被破坏
My number 2 stabilizer has been damaged.
- 我现在在哪儿？
- 这正是我要问你的
- Where am I?
- That's what I was going to ask you.
在Tau Ceti系统里的16号星球 空气密度0.051
Planet 16 in the system Tau Ceti. Air density 0.051.
冷空气伴随暴雨降水的可能性比较大
Cool weather with the possibility of stormy precipitations.
大气分析： 地面有轻度过量的氧气
Analysis of the atmosphere: terrestial with a mild excess of oxygen.
每立方毫米有600324个分子
I count 600324 molecules per cubic millimeter.
不错，至少我能呼吸了
Well, at least I'll be able to breathe.
多了不起的姑娘阿
What marvelous little girls! Hi!
你说英语吗？
Do you speak English?
你说法语吗？（我不确定这句话）
Parlez-vous francais?
等等，我调整一下话筒 一定是银行5的方言
Wait, let me adjust my tongue box. Must be a Galactic 5 dialect.
我已经很多年没滑雪了
But I haven't skied in ages!
那是杜兰杜兰的空间飞船。
But that's Duran Duran's spaceship!
嗨
Hi!
听着，孩子，这个游戏挺有趣 但是不会持续太久的
Listen, children, this game is amusing, but it's gone too far.
我不想伤害你我想知道一些过于这个空间飞行器的情况
I don't want to hurt you. I want to know some things about this spaceship.
快点，解开我，不然我会叫你父母的
Come on, untie me or I'll call your parents.
听起来不错，但是我。
That's very sweet, but I...
不
No!
救命
Help!
住手
Stop!
嗨
Hello!
谢谢
Thank you!
不
No!
我不明白
I can't understand.
你讲法语吗？
Parlez-vous francais?
最好调一个我的话筒
Better adjust my tongue box.
你还好吧？
Are you all right?
还好，你是谁？
I think so... Who are you?
我是马克，汉德，逮捕者。或者翻译成 警察 你是谁？
I am Mark Hand, the catchman. And who are you?
我从地球来，告诉我你所知道的关于这个宇宙飞船的事
I'm from the Planet Earth. Tell me what you know of this spaceship.
我什么也不知道。 在我做逮捕者之前这个飞船就已经在这里了。
I know nothing. It was here when I accepted the job of the catchman.
- 逮捕者？
- 是的，孩子们生活在冰偃
- Catchman?
- Yes. Children live on icey Weir...
知道他们到了可用的年纪
...until they have reached a serviceable age.
- 可用的？
- 然后，我抓住他们，就像你看到的
- Serviceable?
- Then I capture them just as you saw.
- 我把他们交给相关政局。
- 我明白了
- I turn them over to the authorities.
- I see.
谢谢你 你听说过杜兰杜兰这个名字吗？
Thank you. Ever heard the name Duran Duran?
没有，我独自一个人生活在冰偃 就是警察的生活
I know nothing. I live alone on icey Weir. Such is a catchman's life.
只有在sogo你能找到这个问题的答案
Only in Sogo will you find the answer to your question.
-  sogo？在这附近吗？
- 就在冰层的上面
- Sogo? Is it near?
- It's just beyond that ice-deck.
我刚才好像看到了你的航天器在这个湖边？
Did I see your spacecraft at the far edge of this lake?
是的，恐怕已经坏了
Yes, but I'm afraid it's broken down.
- 磁暴毁坏了我的稳定系统。
- 或许，我能帮上忙
- Magnetic storms ruined my stabilizer.
- Perhaps, I can help.
我对磁的东西非常在行。 我服务并维护这个冰艇。
I'm quite experienced mechanically. I service and maintain this icecraft.
- 如果你愿意，我可以带你去你的船。
- .但是没有风
- If you wish, I'll take you to your ship.
- But there's no wind.
抓紧了
Hold on.
- 多可爱的机舱阿
- .风
- What a lovely cabin!
- Wind.
太感谢你的帮助了 我该怎么感谢你呢？
I'm so grateful for your help. How can I ever thank you?
我相信我的政府会回报你的。
I'm sure my government would repay you.
如果有什么我能帮的上忙的尽管告诉我。
If there's anything I can do, please tell me.
你可以让我跟你做爱
You could let me make love to you.
- 做爱？
- 恩
- Make love?
- Yes.
你可能不知道我已经心动了
You don't even know my psycho-cardiogram.
在地球上人们不做爱
On earth people don't make love...
除非他们的心动是完美的汇合了
...unless their psycho-cardiograms are in perfect confluence.
你问我你能为我做些什么，我告诉你了
You asked me what you could do for me. And I told you.
没错 但是我没看出来这么做有什么益处
All right. But I don't see what good it will do.
- 你有药片吗？
- 药片？
- Do you have any pills?
- Pills?
- 不要紧，我这里有一些
- 这是什么药？
- Never mind, I have some here.
- What is this pill?
当然，是一片移情药片。（应该是类似春药的东西）
An exaltation transference pill, of course.
- 我对这个一无所知
- 看出来了
- I know nothing of this.
- I see.
在地球上，在和谐的做爱中有有所心动
On earth when our psycho-cardiograms are in harmony for lovemaking...
我们吃一粒移情药片
...we take an exaltation transference pill.
并且保持这样让展示给你看
And remain like this. Here let me show you.
一分钟或直到实现全面的和谐。
For one minute or until full rapport is achieved.
我不关系那些 我的意思是床
I don't care for that. This is what I mean... the bed!
那个？ 但是没有人做爱几个世纪
That? But nobody's done that for centuries!
除了那些负担不起药钱的穷人或者心理有问题的
Except the poor who can't afford the pill or psycho-cardiograms.
- 为什么不？
- 它阻碍了最高效率。
- Why not?
- It impedes maximum efficiency.
也替代了自我支持和自尊，都是先在可用的。
Also substitutes for ego support and self-esteem are now available.
- 这么说，你不会做了？
- 如果你坚持，我想是这样的
- So, you won't do it?
- If you insist, I guess so.
但是，像那样做真的没有什么意义。
But there's really no point at all in doing it like this.
- 请脱下你的衣服
- 哦
- Without your garments, please.
- Oh.
现在我要看看你的稳定器。
Now I'll have a look at your stabilizers.
知道你的衣服都脱掉了，你可以使用我的皮草， 芭芭丽娜。
Since your garment is torn, help yourself to my furs, Barbarella.
我想我知道哪里出了问题 现在你可以继续去sogo了
I think I've found the trouble. You may proceed now to Sogo.
这那里你能找到杜兰杜兰，如果他还活着
It's there you will find Duran Duran Jr. If he still lives...
好的
Good.
现在，芭芭丽娜 你还不认同我
Now, Barbarella, don't you agree with me...
在一些事情上，还是老式的方法最好？
...that in some things, the old-fashioned ways are best?
什么？  哦，那个
What...? Oh, that.
是的，我不得不承认这一点颇为有趣。
Yes, I must admit it was rather interesting.
尽管如此，这些正在消失
Still, it is distracting.
- 你跟我一起去sogo吗？  sogo-崇光-汗。。。
- 不，我还是喜欢平静的威尔。
- Are you coming with me to Sogo?
- No, I prefer the tranquility of Weir.
Sogo 过于严格，人们都很专制。
Sogo is too strict, the people too dedicated.
在你任务结束的时候你可能还会停经这里
Perhaps you'll stop here again... at the end of your mission.
可能我会的
Yes, perhaps I will...
好吧，再见了，再次谢谢你
Well, goodbye. And thanks again...
为所有的事
For everything.
都是我的荣幸
It was my pleasure.
- 请回报现在的情况
- 你不会明白的
- Please advise present situation.
- You wouldn't understand.
- .稳定器故障
- 我已经修复了
- Stabilizer's malfunctioning.
- I've been repaired in reverse.
我们正在进入 我要激活落地螺钉
We're going in. I'll activate the Terra screw.
芭芭丽娜
Barbarella!
所有的内部系统都马力充足
Full operational power on all subterranean systems.
45度上升
45 degree ascent.
距离表层四分之一到二分之一之间
Quarter-to-half for surfacing.
必须摆脱这个尾巴
Got to get rid of this tail.
- 我完了
- 不
- I'm dead.
- No.
- 我在哪儿？
- 夜城的迷宫
- Where am I?
- In the labyrinth of the City of Night.
- 你是天使吗？
- 我是pygar，最后一个ornithanthrope
- Are you an angel?
- I'm Pygar, the last ornithanthrope.
- 你好
- How do you do?
- And you?
我从地球来 我叫芭芭丽娜
I'm from Planet Earth. My name is Barbarella.
你是柔软的温暖的 我们听说地球上的生物都是冰冷的
But you're soft and warm. We're told that earth beings are cold.
并不是所有的
Not all of us...
我可怜的航天器，看
My poor spaceship. Look at it.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你的眼睛怎么了？
Pygar, what happened to your eyes?
在一场磁暴中我的航天器坠落了，阻碍了我去SOGO。
I fell during a magnetic storm and was carried off to Sogo.
Sogo?
夜城被大暴君统治着，在那里他们瞧不起我
The City of Night ruled by the Great Tyrant. There they blinded me.
我被遗弃在迷宫里等死，直到平教授发现了我。
I was left to die in the labyrinth until Professor Ping found me.
真可怕
That's terrible.
你真的会飞？
Can you really fly?
不，我已经失去了飞的意愿。
No, I've lost the will to fly.
- 多么可怕
- 没事了，都过去了。
- How awful!
- It no longer matters. It's the past.
- 你听说过杜兰杜兰吗
- 杜兰杜兰？
- Have you heard of Duran Duran?
- Duran Duran?
是的，杜兰杜兰 他是从地球来的宇航员。
Yes, Duran Duran. He's an astronaut from Earth.
我不知道这些事
I do not know of such things.
- 也许平教授能帮上忙。
- 平教授？
- Perhaps Professor Ping can help.
- Professor Ping?
他非常聪明而且知道关于SOGO的所有事情。
He's very wise and knows all about Sogo.
- 我在哪里能找到他？
- 他正在跟别人一起吃东西。
- Where can I find him?
- He's with the others, eating.
- 他在那儿。 平教授？
- 平教授？
- He's there. Professor Ping?
- Professor Ping?
- 是的？
- 我是芭芭丽娜。
- Yes?
- My name is Barbarella.
告诉我，你的由来是什么？
Tell me. What is your origin?
你有地球生物的特征 你是女性，对吗？
You have the aspect of an earthling. You are of female gender, right?
是的
That is correct.
- 那是兰花吗？
- 是的
- Is that an orchid?
- Yes.
兰花基本没有食用价值，而且在这种气候下很难生长。
Orchids have very little food value and are hard to grow in this climate.
兰花使大暴君心情很愉快，这样他就不会去怨恨用兰花喂养奴隶的那些花销了。
It amuses the Great Tyrant to resent the expense of feeding orchids to slaves.
- 这是什么地方？
- 那是SOGO，夜城
- What kind of place is this?
- That is Sogo, the City of Night...
被大暴君统治，并且致力于各个方面各种形式都是邪恶的。
...ruled by the Great Tyrant and dedicated to evil in every form.
这个是迷宫。
And this is the labyrinth.
所有不邪恶的都流亡在这个迷宫里
All that is not evil is exiled to the labyrinth.
看
Look!
- 那个绅士是谁？
- 那是一个大怪诞
- Who is that gentleman?
- That is a Grand Grotesque.
这是在迷宫里结束生命的传统的方法
That's the classic way of ending life in the labyrinth.
平教授，你听说过杜兰杜兰吗？
Professor Ping, have you ever heard of Duran Duran?
从地球来的杜兰杜兰？ 是的，没错
Duran Duran from Earth? Yes, indeed.
- 他还活着吗？在哪儿？
- 毫无疑问，在SOGO。
- He's alive? Where?
- In Sogo, no doubt.
我必须马上去那里
I must go there at once.
但是正如你所见，没有人能离开迷宫
But as you've seen, no one may leave the labyrinth.
-我有一个航天器，只要它能运转。
- 我的孩子，也许我能帮助你。
- I have a spaceship, if only it worked.
- My child, perhaps I can help you.
如果你可以 我带你去那里
If only you could... Let me take you there.
你能告诉我怎么走吗？
Pygar, will you show us the way?
- 看起来有什么问题？
- 我觉得是稳定器
- What seems to be the trouble?
- I think it's the stabilizers.
让我们看看
Let's have a look.
Pygar, 笔
Pygar, pen...
给你，谢谢
Here... Thank you.
谢天谢地，hypodontical分子没被破坏
Thank heaven the hypodontical molecules are undamaged.
- 要花费多长时间？
- 几个小时？几天？几周？
- Will it take long?
- Hours? Days? Weeks?
谁知道？
Who knows?
天才是神秘的
Genius is mysterious.
我等不了几周。
I can't wait weeks.
Pygar?
- 你可以带我飞过去，
- 我不能，
- You can fly me there.
- No, I can't.
收缩更大的alea肌肉
Atrophy of the greater alea muscle.
天使听起来是空气动力学的
The angel is aerodynamically sound.
这是一个士气的问题。
It's all a question of morale.
除了等待我们什么也做不了 pygar，你住在哪里？
There's nothing to do but wait. Pygar, where do you live?
来，我告诉你怎么引导我
Come. I'll tell you how to lead me.
- .就在前面
- 是个鸟窝
- Just ahead.
- It's a nest.
- 为什么，是的，我就住在那里
- 太奇妙了
- Why, yes. That's where I live.
- It's marvelous.
很高兴你喜欢它
I'm glad you like it.
等等，他们来了
Wait! They're coming.
救命
Help!
Pygar, 就在你右前方
Pygar, right in front of you.
pygar，不，向右
Pygar, no, to the right.
现在
Now!
- 是什么？
- 大暴君的一个黑卫队。
- What is it?
- One of Great Tyrant's Black Guards.
- 那里没人
- 不，黑卫队是皮革人。
- There isn't anybody in there.
- No, Black Guards are leathermen.
他们没有肉质物质。
They're without fleshy substance.
Pygar, 你救了我的命
Pygar, you saved my life.
Pygar?
Pygar... Oh, Pygar!
当心
Be careful!
Oh, Pygar!
有趣的疗法
Interesting therapy!
- 我重获了飞的意愿
- 我知道
- I've regained the will to fly.
- I know.
Oh,这.这是上天的安排
Oh, it was... It was just heavenly.
- 你能带我去SOGO吗？
- 但是我看不见
- Can you take me to Sogo?
- But I cannot see.
-  Pygar.我来做你的眼睛
- 我觉得这不太可能
- I will be your eyes, Pygar.
- I do not believe it is possible.
我们会被黑卫队巡逻队击落
We'll be shot down by Black Guard patrols.
不带我的小型导弹投影机，我们不会被击落的。
Not with my mini-missile projector, we won't.
- 你还好吧，pygar？
- 是的
- Are you all right, Pygar?
- Yes, thank you.
我不喜欢那个样子
I don't like the looks of that.
向右一点点
A little to the right.
Pygar, 当心
Pygar, watch out!
我抓住他了
I got him!
向右
To the right!
向上，pygar，向上
Up, Pygar, up...
我们可以躲在山后面
We can hide behind that mountain.
Pygar!
- 你还好吧？
- 是的
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
真是时候 我的能量盒完全用完了
Just in time. My energy box is completely dead.
我们现在还安全吧？
Are we all right now?
我想是的。打扰一下
I think so. Excuse me.
我们在这儿，它就在我们正右边。
We're there! It's right below us.
因为你的缘故，我们必须回到回到地面
We must land in a back street, for your sake.
如果在SOGO被发现与一个天使在一起是要被诅咒的。
To be seen in Sogo with an angel would be anathema.
pygar，低头
Pygar, keep your head down.
我们必须找些东西把你的翅膀遮住
Oh my, we must find something to hide your wings.
等等，芭芭丽娜
Wait, Barbarella!
- Pygar.别怕
- 我感觉到了危险，保护好你自己
- Don't be afraid, Pygar.
- I sense danger. Guard yourself.
什么也没有 我确定，来
There's nothing. I promise you. Come!
芭芭丽娜
Barbarella!
pygar，等等我
Pygar, wait for me!
你要我做什么？
What do you want of me?
哦
Oh!
喂，美人，美人
Hello, pretty-pretty.
.喂
Hello.
非常感谢你
Thank you very much.
你想要过来和我一起玩吗？
Do you want to come and play with me?
对于一些像你这样的人我是收取回报的。
For someone like you I charge nothing.
你太可爱了，小可爱
You're very pretty, pretty-pretty.
我的名字不是小可爱 是芭芭丽娜
My name isn't "Pretty-Pretty". It's Barbarella.
- 你在哪里看到一只天使了吗？
- 那个奇怪的鸟？
- Have you seen an angel anywhere?
- The strange bird?
是的
Yes.
是什么在尖叫？
What's that screaming?
很多戏剧性的情况都是开始于尖叫的
A good many dramatic situations begin with screaming.
Pygar!
可怜的pygar
Poor Pygar...
振作起来 在你后面有一个房间
Pygar, back up. There's a room behind you.
他们没有跟过来
They're not following.
Pygar,快
Pygar, come.
告诉我那是什么意思
Tell me what that means.
终极会馆
"Chamber of Ultimate...
...解决方案
...Solution".
我不喜欢那样的声音
I don't like the sound of that.
我们最好离开这里
We'd better get out of here.
这里欢迎那些选择死亡的人
Ye who have chosen to die, be welcome.
要想终止生活的痛苦，你要从三个令人激动
To terminate the bitterness of Ilfe, you may select from three exciting...
并且令人惊讶的死亡方式中选择
...and surprising forms of death.
在你面前的每一扇门后面都有一个死亡方式
One of each awaits behind the doors you see before you.
如果你选择失败，你就会被送给mathmos （mathmos应该是个怪兽的名字），没有申诉
If you fail to choose, you'll be given to the Mathmos. There is no appeal.
下一个解决方案
Next solution.
我们最好冒险尝试一下
We'd better take the chance.
等等
Wait!
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
你最好跟我一起来
You must come with me.
你叫什么名字？ 你是做什么的？
What is your name? What do you do in life?
我是大暴君的礼宾
I'm Concierge to the Great Tyrant.
- 你对于时机的把握很好，祝贺你
- 不是我
- I congratulate you on your timing.
- That wasn't me.
- 那是被大暴君祝贺的 -我明白了
- That was ordained by the Great Tyrant.
- I see.
地板下面的恐怕东西是什么？
What is that horrible thing under the floor?
- 是我的孩子，mathmos
- mathmos？
- That is the Mathmos, my child.
- The Mathmos?
你真的是从地球来的 你不明白
You really are from Earth. You don't understand.
- 恩，不明白
- The Mathmos...
- No.
整个城市是建在一个湖上的
The whole city is built over a lake.
一个非常奇怪的湖。 跟你的成分很像，我生活的能量来源
A very curious lake. Composed like you and I of living energy...
而且一种液态形式的能量
...but energy in liquid form.
它在看我们
And it watches us.
这是磁场，目前正处于正电荷， 它助长了负电荷的震动。
It is magnetic. Being positively charged, it feeds on negative psychic vibrations.
什么是你所谓的“邪恶”
What you would call "evil".
它助长邪恶的思想，行为和躯体。
It thrives on evil thoughts, deeds and flesh.
反过来，它给我们温暖，光明和它自己的生命
In return, it gives us warmth, light and life itself.
但是它有一个可怕的胃口
But it has a terrible appetite.
也许下次我会看到一些
Perhaps you'll see some other time.
Pygar! Pygar!
别担心 你很快就能见到他的
Don't be concerned. You'll see him again soon.
现在，如果你想，请这边走
Now, if you'll just come this way.
坐在这儿 恐怕你得按照我说的做
Here, sit. I'm afraid you must do as I say.
坐在那儿
There, sit.
请向前一点
Forward... Please.
- Oh, Moxys...moxys（人名）
- 什么？
- Oh, Moxys...
- What?
moxys，看，地球生物
Look, Moxys. The earthling.
你得到了她
You get her. Get her now.
礼宾不会让我们玩的。他总是扫我们的兴。不管怎么样我们还是试一试。
The Concierge will never let us. He always spoils our fun. Let's try anyway.
- 地球生物，跟我们一起玩
- 你必须跟我们一起玩
- Play with us, earthling.
- You must play with us.
- 我们有很多洋娃娃
- 我的天啊，你们在这里做什么？
- We have lots of dolls.
- My God, what are they doing here?
Stomoxys（人名）和 Glossina（人名）是大暴君的侄女
Stomoxys and Glossina are nieces of the Great Tyrant.
在我们这里她们非常受欢迎
They're highly favored in our court.
- 为什么不跟我们一起？
- 那不公平
- Why not with us?
- That's not fair.
- 孩子们，大暴君优先
- 我们先看到她的
- The Great Tyrant goes first, children.
- We saw her first.
- 听话，姑娘们
- 站在我旁边
- Be good, girls.
- Stomoxys, Glossina... stay by me.
我的小可爱，我们又见面了
So, my pretty-pretty, we meet again.
你 ！ wench我觉得应该是witch（女巫）单眼睛小女巫
You...! The little one-eyed wench.
你记性很好，小可爱
You have a good memory, Pretty-Pretty.
有时候我想回到我的人民中去，就像他们
Sometimes I like to go among my people... be like them.
普通的，邪恶的，就像你叫的那样
Ordinary. Evil, as you call it.
所以，我是你的单眼睛小情人
So, I'm your little one-eyed wench.
我也是大暴君
I'm also the Great Tyrant.
- 很好
- 它是我乐趣无穷
- Well, that's nice.
- It amuses me immensely.
现在，你想要某个人的特权信息，对吧？
Now, you want some privileged information about a certain man, yes?
是的，我在这里是奉地球总统的命令。
Yes, I'm here on the orders of the President of the Republic of Earth.
- 来这里找杜兰杜兰
- 我不是指他，是天使
- I'm here to find Duran Duran.
- I don't mean him, but the angel!
- Pygar?pygar？
- 是的，pygar
- Pygar?
- Yes, Pygar.
他逃离了迷宫，罪恶阿
He has escaped the labyrinth. Crime!
他摧毁了我黑卫队的12名成员 罪恶
He's destroyed 12 of my Black Guards. Crime!
他竟然敢剥夺整个SOGO城的快乐
And he dares to deprive me of a pleasure unique in Sogo...
...一个地球生物，罪恶，罪恶
...An earthling. Crime! Crime!
- pygar在那儿？
- 你想要找到你羽毛漂亮的朋友？
- Where is Pygar?
- You want your fine-feathered friend?
他在那儿
There he is.
Pygar!pygar
Pygar!
有趣，不是吗？ 小可爱？ 难道你不喜欢玩？
Amusing, isn't it, Pretty-Pretty? Don't you feel like playing?
小可爱 如果你想你可以跟我们一起玩
Pretty-Pretty... You can play with us if you want.
- 好的，为什么不呢？
- 好的，小可爱
- Yes, why not!
- Good, Pretty-Pretty.
Mathmos对你产生影响了
The Mathmos is having its effect on you already.
这是烟雾 他们会让一个人有想玩的念头
It's the fumes. They make one want to play.
- 摧毁这个天使
- 什么？
- Decrucify the angel!
- What?
摧毁他，不然我就溶化掉你的脸
Decrucify him or I'll melt your face!
我的脸 我漂亮的脸蛋
My face! My beautiful face...
- 住手，不然我就射击了
- 住手
- Stop or I'll shoot.
- Stop!
-我的脸
- 我警告你
- My face!
- I warn you.
你怎么敢威胁伤害我的脸
How dare you endanger my face!
陛下，观察她的能量扣
Observe her power buckle, Your Majesty.
能量耗竭了，这个武器就像孩子的玩具一点用都没有了
Depleted. This weapon is as harmless as a child's toy.
所以，这只是一个骗局，是吧？ 你应该保存你的伎俩
So, it was a trick, was it? You should have saved your tricks for...
- 为那些鸟，我的陛下？
- 是的，那些鸟
- For the birds, Your Majesty?
- Yes, the birds.
那些鸟 把它给那些鸟
The birds. Give it to the birds.
你必须
You must...
告诉我，我奇妙的，迷糊的
Tell me, my fancy, fuzzy freak.
当你和芭芭丽娜做爱的时候你会想什么？
What do you think of when you make love to Barbarella?
做爱？我不明白
Make love? I do not understand.
别在我面前害羞，你现在没有立场可言。
Don't be coy with me. You are in no position.
如果你只有一只眼睛，你就会看到我是一个多么快乐的人
If only you had one eye, you would see what a delight I am.
我的脸，我的身体
My face, my body.
我所以的东西都是快乐的
All my things are a delight.
讲究的快乐
An exquisite delight.
- 你想要什么？
- 我要与你分享我的快乐
- What is it you want?
- I shall share my delights with you.
你要和我做爱
You shall make love to me.
一个天使不做爱 天使就是爱
An angel doesn't make love. An angel is love.
那你就是一个死鸭子了
Then you're a dead duck.
卫队
Guards!
把这个带翅膀的水果蛋糕给Mathmos
To the Mathmos with this winged fruitcake.
走吧，。。进来
Come along... Get inside.
哦，我亲爱的，我。。
Oh, how darling. Oh, my...
救命
Help!
这实在是太富有诗意的死亡方式
This is really much too poetic a way to die.
- 密码，快
- 我不明白
- Password, quickly.
- I don't understand.
- 你是一个政治犯吗？
- 我不这样认为
- You're a political prisoner?
- I don't think so.
- 你不是我们中的一个？
- 我来自地球
- Are you not one of us?
- I'm from Earth.
地球？革命的星球 你要加入我们的事业吗？
Earth...? Planet of the Revolutions. Will you join our cause?
什么事业？你是谁？
What cause? Who are you?
我是Dildano，革命部队的首领，这是我们的总部
I'm Dildano, head of the Revolutionary Forces. This is our headquarters.
- 革命万岁
- 大革命
- Long live the Revolution!
- The Revolution!
巡逻部队报告
Patrol report.
立即开始第二个层次的。。。。 不，采取秘密通道
Second level immediately... No, take the secret passage.
那扇门
The door!
你是典型的地球女人吗？
Are you typical of earth women?
我是一般的，并不是典型
I'm about average.
- 我是怎么从那个鸟笼里出来的？
- 通过一个秘密的斜道。
- How did I get out of the bird cage?
- Through a secret escape chute.
我们已经在全城建立了秘密通道
We've established secret escape chutes throughout the city.
为了保护我们的组织。
It's for the protection of our group.
- 我知道你救了我的命
- 没有事业的生活是没有效果的。
- You realize you saved my life.
- A life without cause is without effect.
我相信我的政府会回报你的。
I'm sure my government would repay you.
地球女人，我能告诉你我喜欢什么吗？
Earthwoman, shall I tell you what I would like?
我想我知道
I think I know.
不，不是那样的 就像在地球上，那个药片
No! Not like that. Like on earth... the pill.
- 我有药片
- 但是
- I have the pill!
- But...
我们不能按照你的方式做吗？ 我不想改变你的传统
Couldn't we do it your way? I don't want to change your traditions.
我不是奴隶
I'm not a savage.
- 药片
- 好吧
- The pill.
- Right.
我等这个经历已经等了五年了
Five years I've waited for this experience.
等等
Wait!
革命万岁
Long live the Revolution!
我的组织必须。。。。
My group must...
喂！
Hello!
抱歉
Sorry!
我的组织必须有更多。。。
My group must have more...
你从哪里得到的这些药片？ 只要地球人知道这些药片
Where did you get those pills? Only Earth people know of those pills.
你在那里，有什么消息吗？
You there... What news?
在能发动进攻之前我的组织必须有更多的武器
My group must have more weapons before we can launch an attack.
- 回到原位，等待命令
- 好的
- Back to position. Await your orders.
- Right.
- 你会接受到命令的
- 革命万岁
- You will receive your orders!
- Long live the Revolution!
那扇门，门
The door... the door... Door!
你必须告诉我，是一个地球人给了你这些药片吗？
You must tell me! Did an earth person give you those pills?
- 一个叫杜兰杜兰的人？ -没错
- A man called Duran Duran?
- That's correct.
- 他在哪里？
- 他来的时候给了我这些药片
- Where is he?
- He gave me the pills when he arrived.
从那以后就没见过他了，我觉得他还活这，可能在城堡里
Haven't see him since. I think he's alive... probably in the castle.
- 你有什么东西我可以 。。。。
- 当然，一件秘密制服
- Do you have anything I can...
- Of course, have a secret uniform.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我被我的政府派到这里来找杜兰
I was sent here by my government to find Duran Duran.
你的政府？
Your government...?
那意味这你有一个空间飞行器和武器
That must mean that you have a spacecraft and weapons.
是的，当然，我不喜欢这个红色
Yes, of course... I don't like this red.
你能借你的设备给我们吗？为了我们的事业
Would you lend your equipment to our cause?
不，我不能那样做 除非我能把握自己的任务完成。
No, I couldn't do that. Not till I've completed my own mission.
- 也许我们能做笔交易
- 怎么讲？
- Perhaps we can strike a bargain.
- What do you mean?
只有黑皇后知道杜兰杜兰在哪里
Only the Black Queen knows the whereabouts of Duran Duran.
每当她脆弱的时候她都会在她秘密的梦想会所里。
Her one vulnerable moment is when she's in her secret Chamber of Dreams.
- 梦想会所？
- 是的
- Chamber of Dreams?
- Yes.
她独自住在Mathmos上面的一个房间里
She sleeps alone in a room above the Mathmos...
被一堵能量墙包围着， 只有她有一把秘密的钥匙
...surrounded by a wall of energy, to which she has a secret key.
这个，另外一把钥匙，现在在我这里
There is, however, a second key, which is now in my possession.
我要找到杜兰杜兰 我要捕获黑皇后
You want to find Duran Duran. I want to capture the Black Queen.
你懂了我的意思吗？
You follow my meaning?
如果你真的有另外一把钥匙，为什么你一只没用它？
If you really have a second key, why haven't you used it already?
因为我们的力量还不够强大。
Because our forces are not yet strong enough.
要捕获黑皇后，我们需要有一次军事政变
To capture the Black Queen, we need to have a military coup.
用你的飞行器和武器我们就能做到
We can do this with your weaponry and spacecraft.
控制住黑皇后，你就能知道在哪里能找到杜兰杜兰了
Get control of the Black Queen and you'll know where to find Duran Duran.
- 好的，我明白了
- 好
- Yes, I see.
- Good.
我需要6个小时准备袭击
I need six hours to ready my attack.
首先，我们需要联系上平教授， 看看阿尔法7号是否已经修好。
First, we need to reach Professor Ping to find out if Alpha 7 has been repaired.
顺利完成 我有一个秘密的无线电发射器。
Easily done. I have a secret radio transmitter.
平教授呼叫总部 平教授呼叫总部
Professor Ping to Headquarters... Professor Ping to Headquarters.
- 平教授呼叫总部
- 不
- Professor Ping to Headquar...
- No!
总部呼叫平教授 总部呼叫平教授
Headquarters to Professor Ping... Headquarters to Professor Ping.
- 请进
- 我是平，我能听清你说话
- Come in, please.
- This is Ping. I hear you loud and clear.
- 我有地球生物。。。
- 芭芭丽娜
- I have the earthling...
- Barbarella.
...芭芭丽娜和我在一起，我们能用她的飞行器和武器
...Barbarella with me. We can use her spacecraft and weaponry.
- 她的飞行器还能运行吗？
- 是的，飞行器已经能飞了
- Is her spacecraft in working order?
- Yes, the craft is ready for flight now.
- 太棒了
- 不过，还有一点不足
- Excellent!
- There is one danger, however.
黑卫队的人巡逻时发现了飞行器， 并可能回来破坏飞行器。
A Black Guard patroller spotted the craft and may return to destroy it.
谢天谢地
Good heavens!
我已经通过编程让飞行器 在迷宫外面的隐蔽地方躲起来了。
I have programmed the craft to go a hidden location outside the labyrinth.
- 你是一个巫师，平
- 飞行器现在起飞了
- You're a wizard, Ping.
- It's taking off even now.
它在那儿，完美的飞行模式
There it goes. Perfect flight pattern.
我们的。。。是1600小时 我们的密码是。。。
Our rendez-vous point is 1600 hours. Our password is...
"Llanfairpwllgwyngyllgogerychwyrn- drobwllllantysiliogogogoch."
你的意思是秘密是。。
You mean the secret is...
"Llanfairpwllgwyngyllgogerychwyrn- drobwllllantysiliogogogoch."
正是
Exactly!
- 对吗？
- 对
- Right?
- Right.
总部签署 总部签署
Headquarters signing off. Headquarters signing off.
时机成熟，黑皇后在她的梦想会管。
The time is right. The Queen is in her Chamber of Dreams.
- 钥匙呢？
- 钥匙
- What about the key?
- The key!
- 秘密钥匙在那儿
- 哪儿？
- There is the secret key.
- Where?
是隐形的，只有隐形钥匙能打开隐形的墙
It's invisible. Only an invisible key can open an invisible wall.
哪里？
Where?
Mathmos... 钥匙
My Mathmos... the key!
钥匙
The key...
我有
I have it!
我会把它系在你神秘的脖子上
I'll put it around your secret neck.
看不见的
Invisible.
现在，这张秘密地图会指引你去第12走廊。
Now, the secret map that will lead you to the 12th corridor.
什么走廊？
What corridor?
好的！
Good!
这边走
This way!
"Llanfairpwllgwyngyllgogerychwyrn- drobwllllantysiliogogogoch."   （是一串密码）
"Llanfairpwllgwyngyllgogerychwyrn- drobwllllantysiliogogogoch."
革命万岁
Long live the Revolution!
.一会儿就好
One moment.
我正好不负责管子的样式。
I'm just not the tube type.
打扰一下，你能告诉我第12走廊怎么走吗？
Excuse me. Could you tell me how to get to the 12th corridor?
我喜欢你
I have a taste for you.
- 那是什么？？
- 人的本质
- What is it?
- Essence of Man.
人的本质？
Essence of Man?
所以，你逃脱了那些鸟
So, you escaped the birds!
刚刚好 到我娱乐的时间了
Just as well. It is my turn for some amusement.
跟我来
Come with me.
这边请
This way, please!
- 这是什么东西？
- 你很快就知道了，我亲爱的
- What is this thing?
- You will soon see, my dear.
刽子手和各种各样的年轻女人的奏鸣曲
"Sonata for Executioner and Various Young Women".
这。。。。从某个意识上说很好，不是吗？
It's... sort of nice, isn't it?
是的，开头不错
Yes. It is nice... In the beginning.
等到调子变化 可能也会变化你的调子
Wait until the tune changes. It may change your tune as well.
天啊，你什么意思？
Goodness, what do you mean?
当我们达到高潮 你就会没有痛苦的死去
When we reach the crescendo, you will die... of pleasure.
你的生命会结束的很迅速，但是很美，非常美
Your end will be swift, but sweet... very sweet.
这是什么？我不相信
What is this? I don't believe it.
不可能的
It couldn't be!
可怜的姑娘，你对我的机器做过什么？
Wretched girl... What have you done to my excessive machine?
你已经撤销了它 撤销了我，看，看
You've undone it. You've undone me. Look, look!
能量舱正在变小你把他们捆起来
Energy cables are shrinking. You've turned them into faggots.
你把这些使用过渡的机器烧毁了 你炸掉了所有的燃料
You've burned out the excessive machine. You've blown all its fuses.
我的天啊
My goodness!
你浪费了所有的能源 它无法跟着你了
You've exhausted its power. It couldn't keep up with you.
难以置信，你是什么样的女孩？ 难道你不羞愧吗？
Incredible! What kind of girl are you? Have you no shame?
羞愧，为你感到羞愧 你会为此付出代价的。
Shame! Shame on you! You'll pay for this.
我已经给你准备了一些东西 祝你死的愉快
I've got something for you. You'll wish you had died of pleasure.
现在你应该学习睫毛的智慧。
Now you shall learn the wisdom of the lash.
你对我做的还不够吗？
Haven't you done enough to me?
我会对你做一些超越所有已知哲学的事
I'll do things to you that are beyond all known philosophies.
等我拿到我的设备在做
Wait until I get my devices.
杜兰杜兰？
Duran Duran?
哦，认出我了？
Oh, recognized me?
认出你？
Recognized you?
我从来没有认出你。 我之前以为你只有25岁，发生了什么？
I'd never have recognized you. I thought you were only 25. What happened?
- mathmos发挥了它的作用/功效
-  你现在是30岁了。
- The Mathmos is not without its effect.
- But you've aged 30 years!
Mathmos有它自己的营养方式 作为回报，它教给你真理
The Mathmos has its own means of nourishment. In return, it teaches truth.
杜兰杜兰博士，你能递给我一件衣服吗？
Dr. Duran, could you hand me a garment?
地球的总统派我过来救你
The President of the Republic of Earth sent me here to save you.
- 并且带你回地球
- 地球？ 永远不
- And to return you to Earth.
- Earth planet? Never!
我能告诉你为什么吗？ 因为我知道的太多了
Shall I tell you why? Because I know too much.
在崇光我学到了真理和本质
Here in Sogo I have learned truth and essence.
我说的是尊严，崇高的邪恶。
I speak of the dignity, the nobility of pure Evil.
请把靴子给我
My boots, please.
以人为本，道德，原则 都是垃圾，毫无疑义
Humanism! Morals! Principles...! It's rubbish! Nonsense!
我只说真想和本质。
I speak only of truth and of essence.
-Positronic射线在哪儿？
- 他就是
- Where is the Positronic Ray?
- So, that's it.
这个是做什么用的？
What does it do?
de-miniminized 到了第4级 所有人和物体都在其路径
All persons and objects within its path are de-miniminized to the 4th level.
- 你的意思是。。。？
- 没错
- You mean...?
- That's right.
不可逆转的取代第四层面。
Replaced in the 4th dimension irretrievably.
- 太可怕了
- 是的，难道不是吗？
- But that's monstrous!
- Yes, it is. Isn't it?
在SOGO你为什么不携带武器？
Why didn't you take power here in Sogo?
黑皇后必须第一个被摧毁
The Black Queen must first be destroyed.
正像你所知道的她总是被她的黑卫队包围着。
But as you know, she is always surrounded by her Black Guards.
第一个成功杀死她的人会被立即处死。
Whoever succeeds in killing her will be put immediately to a horrible death.
因此，我要谨慎。
Hence, my prudence.
我发现了这个可怕的想法， 我对别人做了什么别人也会对我这样做 （以牙还牙吧）
I find horrible the idea that one could do to me that which I do to others.
但是我听说黑皇后在睡觉的时候很脆弱
But I was told the Black Queen is vulnerable while she sleeps.
是的，在梦想会馆里没有黑卫队
Oh, yes. There are no Black Guards in the Chamber of Dreams.
那是因为会馆没有入口
That's because there's no access to the Chamber.
现在是我享受的时候了 也就是你的死期了
But, now's time for my pleasure... and your death.
等等
Wait!
我知道你是怎么进入梦想会馆的
I know how you can enter the Chamber of Dreams.
- 怎么？说
- 我有钥匙
- How? Speak!
- I have the key.
- 钥匙是什么样子的？
- 是透明的，不可见的
- What does it look like?
- It's invisible.
带我去梦想会馆
Take me to the Chamber of Dreams.
芭芭丽娜，在你后面
After you, Barbarella.
向右
To the right, Barbarella...
现在向左
Now, to the left...
停
Stop.
打开它
Open it!
- 这一定就是透明墙
- 是的，钥匙呢？
- This must be the invisible wall.
- Yes. Now, where's the key?
- 来吧，别拖了
- 我正在找钥匙孔
- Come on, stop stalling.
- I'm trying to find the keyhole.
你被困住了，你被困在了梦想会馆里
You're trapped. You're trapped in the Chamber of Dreams.
-  Mathmos会吃了你
-  我的陛下
- The Mathmos will devour you.
- Your Majesty!
没用的，我有两把钥匙。 这堵墙是被永久密封的。
It's no use. I've got the two keys. The wall's sealed for all eternity.
杜兰杜兰博士，别犯傻了
Dr. Duran, give up this madness!
- 跟我回地球
- 除非作为地球的征服者我才回去
- Return to Earth with me now.
- I'll return to Earth, but as its conqueror!
多亏你，黑皇后，我最后的障碍，已经被清除掉了。
Thanks to you, the Queen, my last obstacle, has been removed.
谢谢你，芭芭丽娜 现在什么也阻止不了我 今天，SOGO城的主人
Thank you, Barbarella.
Nothing can stop me now. Today, Master of Sogo...
明天，地球的主人，银河系的主人，宇宙的主人
Tomorrow, Master of the Earth, Master of the Galaxy, Master of the Universe!
告诉我，我的好的，带羽毛的朋友，你觉得怎么样？
Tell me, my fine, feathered friend, what do you think of...
你什么时候和芭芭丽娜做爱？
...when you make love to Barbarella?
一个天使不做爱的 天使就是爱的象征。
An angel doesn't make love. An angel is love.
醒醒，我的陛下 你必须起来
Wake up, Your Majesty! You must wake up.
Vade retro（不知道啥意思）地球女孩 我知道你并不是真的存在
Vade retro, Earthgirl! I know you don't really exist.
可能是，我的陛下 但是我们最好坚持我们看到的。 （意思是她是真实存在的）
That may be, Your Majesty. But we'd better stick to what we see.
可怜的姑娘，你都做了什么？ 我睡觉的时候没人能进来
Wretched girl, what have you done? No one must enter while I sleep.
你的礼宾正在接管王位。
Your Concierge is taking over the throne.
- 你在说什么？
- 真的，他偷走了你的钥匙。
- What are you saying?
- It's true. He's taken your key.
- 我们被锁起来了，我的陛下
- 钥匙，他偷走了钥匙！！
- We're locked in, Your Majesty.
- The key. He's stolen the key!
我们完了，完了
We are doomed... Doomed!
他说Mathmos会吃了我们 他什么意思？
He said the Mathmos would devour us. What did he mean?
据说除非我一个人在梦想会馆
It is said that unless I am alone in my Chamber of Dreams...
Mathmos就会要求我
...the Mathmos will claim me.
-是王位房间
- 我能看到所有的城市和迷宫。
- It's the throne room.
- I can see all of the City and labyrinth.
不幸的是，这个屏幕是单向的， 我能看到所有的城市和迷宫，但是别人看不到我。
Unfortunately, it's a one-way screen.
没有能能看到那只血腥的狗把我锁了起来
No one can see that bloody dog has locked me in.
陛下，我们正在受到攻击 迷宫里的生物
Your Majesty! We're under attack. The creatures in the labyrinth.
他们正在起义
They're revolting!
他怎敢打算我的加冕 派遣空中舰队
How dare he interrupt my coronation! Dispatch the air armada!
迅速，陛下，迷宫
Quick, Your Majesty, the labyrinth.
是Dildano，他救了我们
It's Dildano. He will save us.
- 陛下，他们都被消灭了
- 好样的
- Your Majesty, they're all destroyed.
- Good.
- 迷宫里没有留下一个生物
- 飞行器也没有
- Not a creature left in the labyrinth.
- No aircraft left!
他们有地球上的武器
They have Earth weapons!
傻瓜，骗子，蠢才 每件事都要我自己做吗？
Fool! Liar! Idiots! Must I do everything myself?
- 我必须消灭这群乌合之众
- 他会使用Positronic射线
- I must destroy this rabble.
- He'll use the Positronic Ray.
它起作用了
It works!
它起作用了，起作用了
It works... It works.
所有都失去了
All is lost.
我必须死，非常好但是我是笑到最后的那一个。
I must die, very well, but it is I who shall have the last laugh.
低能儿不知道大暴君的秘密。
The imbecile doesn't know the secret of the Great Tyrant.
最高级别的武器 我要释放Mathmos
The supreme weapon. I shall free the Mathmos.
- 你认为i那明智吗？
- Sogo城会消失的
- Do you think that's wise?
- Sogo will disappear.
它将会结束了，启示录
It will be the end. The Apocalypse!
- 我们在哪里
- 在Mathmos里，所以人都活着。
- Where are we?
- In the Mathmos. And alive!
我能看到，为什么？
I can see that, but why?
Mathmos制造了这个气泡来保护它自己
The Mathmos created this bubble to protect itself from your innocence.
太好了
That's nice.
不，不，住手，我命令它
No, no, stop! I command it.
我是杜兰杜兰
I'm Duran Duran.
我是Mathmos的主人
I'm Master of the Mathmos.
回落
Fall back!
我要用我的Positronic射线毁灭你
I'll destroy you with my Positronic Ray.
你太好了，你让Mathmos呕吐了
You're so good, you make the Mathmos vomit.
你对pygar做了什么？
Pygar! What did you do to Pygar?
他被送到了Mathmos，但是他不想你更容易被消化
He was sent to the Mathmos, but was no more digestible than you are.
你不能死
You can't be dead.
芭芭丽娜，你赢了， 但是地球失去了她最后一个伟大的独裁统治着
You win, Barbarella. But the earth has lost its last great dictator.
Positronic射线天才
The genius of the Positronic Ray...
为什么你不给他一个嘴对嘴的吻？
Why don't you give him a mouth-to-mouth?
我有一个更好的主意
I have a better idea.
求求你了，pygar，求求你了
Please... Pygar, please.
请醒醒
Please wake up!
我们必须飞回到我的飞行器 你还有力气吗？
We must fly back to my spaceship. Do you have the strength?
pygar，她对你做了那么多可怕的事， 你为什么还要救她？
Pygar, why did you save her after all the terrible things she did to you?
一个没有记忆的天使
An angel has no memory!